[
  {
    "id": "22f58886-f92e-48c1-96a8-21576152a670",
    "reference": "1- Psalm 49:3 \u201cMy mouth shall speak wisdom\u201d",
    "question": "According to thy name, O God, so it thy praise unto the ends of the earth: thy right hand is full of ___.",
    "options": [
      "Blessing",
      "Support",
      "Righteousness",
      "Respect"
    ],
    "answer": "Righteousness",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a3e26b19-b8f2-466e-bd4e-ce0eb7068afb",
    "reference": "1- Psalm 49:3 \u201cMy mouth shall speak wisdom\u201d",
    "question": "Can anyone who trust in their wealth or boast themselves in their multitude of their riches redeem their brother?",
    "options": [
      "Sometimes",
      "No",
      "In some countries",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8ce07cc1-a40b-44df-8f7f-825580d916d1",
    "reference": "2- James 1:17 \u201cEvery good gift and every perfect gift is from above\u201d",
    "question": "For when he dieth he shall carry ___ away: his glory shall not descend after him.",
    "options": [
      "Take",
      "Himself",
      "Nothing",
      "Christ"
    ],
    "answer": "Nothing",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e7749b32-1c8c-474a-b9f4-4858009cd49e",
    "reference": "2- James 1:17 \u201cEvery good gift and every perfect gift is from above\u201d",
    "question": "Who did James address his letter to?",
    "options": [
      "God",
      "Jesus",
      "Christians",
      "The twelve tribes"
    ],
    "answer": "The twelve tribes",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ede746fa-dc94-4617-ba9e-5c0133b0d494",
    "reference": "2- James 1:17 \u201cEvery good gift and every perfect gift is from above\u201d",
    "question": "If any of you lack ___, let him ask of God, that giveth to all men liberally, and upbraided not; and it shall be given him.",
    "options": [
      "Money",
      "Gifts",
      "Wisdom",
      "Patience"
    ],
    "answer": "Wisdom",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "21959cfc-36b1-48f7-8bef-3f866de82d53",
    "reference": "3- Hebrews 4:12 \u201cThe word of God is living\u201d",
    "question": "___ is the man that endureth temptation: for when he is tried, he shall receive the crown of life, which the Lord hath promised to them that love him.",
    "options": [
      "Blessed",
      "Honored",
      "Great",
      "Prudent"
    ],
    "answer": "Blessed",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3d102ffa-495f-4a3f-ac3f-c3379fe221dd",
    "reference": "3- Hebrews 4:12 \u201cThe word of God is living\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the great priest?",
    "options": [
      "James",
      "John",
      "Jesus",
      "Mark"
    ],
    "answer": "Jesus",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1311d13a-9647-45bd-9a89-79010daa1d27",
    "reference": "3- Hebrews 4:12 \u201cThe word of God is living\u201d",
    "question": "___ not your hearts, as in the provocation, in the day of temptation in the wilderness:",
    "options": [
      "Trust",
      "Harden",
      "Believed",
      "Blessed"
    ],
    "answer": "Harden",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "64d3c03c-4502-41fd-a874-15d77ec90e38",
    "reference": "4- Philippians 4:13 \u201cI can do all things through Christ who strengthens me\u201d",
    "question": "What is sharper than any twoedged sword?",
    "options": [
      "Guns",
      "Knifes",
      "The word",
      "Christ"
    ],
    "answer": "The word",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "882d99b6-2ca9-432e-813e-fc04cfca043f",
    "reference": "4- Philippians 4:13 \u201cI can do all things through Christ who strengthens me\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the author of the book of Philippians?",
    "options": [
      "Philip",
      "Paul",
      "Timotheus",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4c8e400f-3a3b-4e1c-b1b8-2c397283f990",
    "reference": "4- Philippians 4:13 \u201cI can do all things through Christ who strengthens me\u201d",
    "question": "Be careful for ____; but in everything by prayer and supplication with thanksgiving let your request be made known unto God.",
    "options": [
      "Life",
      "Success",
      "Nothing",
      "Salvation"
    ],
    "answer": "Nothing",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "68a87d03-299b-4427-9f19-4c2e96798bab",
    "reference": "5- Romans 15:13 \u201cMay the God of hope fill you with all joy and peace\u201d",
    "question": "But my God shall supply ___ your need according to his riches in glory by Christ Jesus.",
    "options": [
      "Some of",
      "Whatever",
      "All",
      "Regardless of"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e91bf093-0379-4bba-af0a-1d5b33263170",
    "reference": "5- Romans 15:13 \u201cMay the God of hope fill you with all joy and peace\u201d",
    "question": "Now the God of ___ and consolation grant you to be like-minded one toward another according to Christ Jesus.",
    "options": [
      "Power",
      "Peace",
      "Abraham",
      "Patience"
    ],
    "answer": "Patience",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7cb59e24-074f-4bb2-9d5a-d5946105db8b",
    "reference": "5- Romans 15:13 \u201cMay the God of hope fill you with all joy and peace\u201d",
    "question": "Let us therefore follow after the things which make for ___, and things wherewith one may edify another.",
    "options": [
      "Understanding",
      "Peace",
      "Love",
      "Knowledge"
    ],
    "answer": "Peace",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "daff7a41-e0d4-48c9-82f5-772064dae1b1",
    "reference": "6- Acts 3:19 \u201cRepent therefore and be converted\u201d",
    "question": "Nevertheless, brethren, I have written the more boldly unto you in some sort, as putting you in mind, because of the ___ that is given to me of God.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Fear",
      "Imagination",
      "Grace"
    ],
    "answer": "Grace",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fc41dfbb-70bf-404b-b1ce-51f21e82c09d",
    "reference": "6- Acts 3:19 \u201cRepent therefore and be converted\u201d",
    "question": "Who said \u201cSilver and gold have I none\u201d?",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Timothy",
      "Peter",
      "Mark"
    ],
    "answer": "Peter",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "676a9577-ccdf-41d9-b5e2-64af22946485",
    "reference": "6- Acts 3:19 \u201cRepent therefore and be converted\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the Prince of life?",
    "options": [
      "Abraham",
      "Jacob",
      "Jesus",
      "Joseph"
    ],
    "answer": "Jesus",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7f05581e-7cda-4018-b0ce-60ff98531919",
    "reference": "7-1 Corinthians 10:12 \u201cTake heed lest [you] fall\u201d",
    "question": "And it shall come to pass, that every soul, which will not hear that prophet, shall be ___ from among the people.",
    "options": [
      "Ignored",
      "Neglected",
      "Chosen",
      "Destroyed"
    ],
    "answer": "Destroyed",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e9dbf361-fa16-452b-80a6-e4bdbd799b08",
    "reference": "7-1 Corinthians 10:12 \u201cTake heed lest [you] fall\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the author of the book of I Corinthians?",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Paul",
      "Jesus",
      "Mark"
    ],
    "answer": "Paul",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "638fc957-43bc-4401-af76-67b093d007c8",
    "reference": "7-1 Corinthians 10:12 \u201cTake heed lest [you] fall\u201d",
    "question": "Wherefore, my dearly beloved, flee from ___.",
    "options": [
      "Stinginess",
      "Mockery",
      "Idolatry",
      "Slavery"
    ],
    "answer": "Idolatry",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fc66b82d-2155-47c1-9f0c-c12c05b65cbc",
    "reference": "8- 2 Corinthians 3:17 \u201cWhere the Spirit of the Lord is there is liberty\u201d",
    "question": "Let no man seek his own, but every man another's ___.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Wealth",
      "Protection",
      "Well-being"
    ],
    "answer": "Wealth",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9ca2eaf2-c6c9-4ed8-9a91-08a05422601d",
    "reference": "8- 2 Corinthians 3:17 \u201cWhere the Spirit of the Lord is there is liberty\u201d",
    "question": "For if the ministration of condemnation be glory, much more doth the ministration of righteousness exceed in ___.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Patience",
      "Glory",
      "Peace"
    ],
    "answer": "Glory",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7dc5e25d-a29d-4915-bee0-7c48c4b6603b",
    "reference": "8- 2 Corinthians 3:17 \u201cWhere the Spirit of the Lord is there is liberty\u201d",
    "question": "Lest Satan should get an advantage of us: for we are not ___ of his devices.",
    "options": [
      "Pursuers",
      "In favor",
      "Alarm",
      "Ignorant"
    ],
    "answer": "Ignorant",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "83c2e303-1457-4d89-8e78-55d3e717fa01",
    "reference": "9- Galatians 5:1 \u201cStand fast therefore in the liberty [of Christ]\u201d",
    "question": "But even unto this day, when Moses is read, the veil is upon their ___.",
    "options": [
      "Face",
      "Lips",
      "Heart",
      "House"
    ],
    "answer": "Heart",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f360b6c9-a36b-4d5d-b36b-3301843ab231",
    "reference": "9- Galatians 5:1 \u201cStand fast therefore in the liberty [of Christ]\u201d",
    "question": "The ___ of the Lord Jesus Christ, and the love of God, and the communion of the Holy Ghost, be with you all.",
    "options": [
      "Name",
      "Grace",
      "Support",
      "Blessing"
    ],
    "answer": "Grace",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6491bf6b-536d-4c44-a6ac-fa631e6caa23",
    "reference": "9- Galatians 5:1 \u201cStand fast therefore in the liberty [of Christ]\u201d",
    "question": "But as then he that was born after the flesh persecuted him that was born after the ___, even so it is now.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Blood",
      "King",
      "Spirit"
    ],
    "answer": "Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b1ba9ec5-7337-4e5d-ab5c-f2ff40413911",
    "reference": "10- Ephesians 1:7 \u201cIn [Christ] we have redemption through His blood\u201d",
    "question": "For all the law is fulfilled in one word, even in this; Thou shalt ___ thy neighbor as thyself.",
    "options": [
      "Support",
      "Heal",
      "Love",
      "Know"
    ],
    "answer": "Love",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dc15bbb9-d0b4-4858-a66e-59c93b738aa0",
    "reference": "10- Ephesians 1:7 \u201cIn [Christ] we have redemption through His blood\u201d",
    "question": "When were we chosen by God?",
    "options": [
      "When we were baptized",
      "When we first prayed to him",
      "Before the foundation of the world",
      "We were never chosen"
    ],
    "answer": "Before the foundation of the world",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4e7571ca-6419-4704-8705-14597bbd1c15",
    "reference": "10- Ephesians 1:7 \u201cIn [Christ] we have redemption through His blood\u201d",
    "question": "That we should be to the ___ of his glory, who first trusted in Christ.",
    "options": [
      "Praise",
      "Servant",
      "Friend",
      "Priest"
    ],
    "answer": "Praise",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "976e210a-5f23-45df-a036-988b6e399b96",
    "reference": "11- Ephesians 2:10 \u201cWe are His workmanship\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the head of the Church?",
    "options": [
      "The pastor",
      "The priest",
      "The Queen",
      "Jesus"
    ],
    "answer": "Jesus",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d22671ee-86e3-4445-8b5a-aea6e49c5dbd",
    "reference": "11- Ephesians 2:10 \u201cWe are His workmanship\u201d",
    "question": "But God, who is rich in ___, for his great love wherewith he loved us.",
    "options": [
      "Power",
      "Mercy",
      "Love",
      "Grace",
      "a c & d"
    ],
    "answer": "Mercy",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2fb3a8ce-99f9-4023-ad1b-7e464575c8a4",
    "reference": "11- Ephesians 2:10 \u201cWe are His workmanship\u201d",
    "question": "For he is our ___, who hath made both one, and hath broken down the middle wall of partition between us.",
    "options": [
      "Lord",
      "Savior",
      "Peace",
      "King"
    ],
    "answer": "Peace",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ae3592b3-ba83-4bea-b858-f233e27e3cc5",
    "reference": "12- Philippians 3:14 \u201cI press toward the goal for the prize\u201d",
    "question": "And hath put all things under his __, and gave him to be the head over all things to the church.",
    "options": [
      "Feet",
      "Control",
      "Hands",
      "Hope"
    ],
    "answer": "Feet",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "458fe289-9532-4bca-afbf-04fe2c284164",
    "reference": "12- Philippians 3:14 \u201cI press toward the goal for the prize\u201d",
    "question": "For we are the circumcision which worship God in the ___, and rejoice in Christ Jesus, and have no confidence in the flesh.",
    "options": [
      "Church",
      "Spirit",
      "Heart",
      "House"
    ],
    "answer": "Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e167c204-f661-4e6f-9f52-64e46f98b993",
    "reference": "12- Philippians 3:14 \u201cI press toward the goal for the prize\u201d",
    "question": "That I may know him, and the power of his ___, and the fellowship of his sufferings, being made comfortable unto his death.",
    "options": [
      "Strength",
      "Love",
      "Resurrection",
      "Redemption"
    ],
    "answer": "Resurrection",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "94cbe67e-207f-43eb-a6ce-11d02881834a",
    "reference": "13- John 15:3 \u201cYou are already clean because of the word spoken to you\u201d",
    "question": "For our conversation is in __; from whence also we look for the savior, the Lord Jesus Christ.",
    "options": [
      "Wisdom",
      "Love",
      "The spirit",
      "Heaven"
    ],
    "answer": "Heaven",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bbb22568-b51c-42c9-8bb0-d80d76154d10",
    "reference": "13- John 15:3 \u201cYou are already clean because of the word spoken to you\u201d",
    "question": "But that the world may know that I __ the father; and as the Father gave me commandment, even so  I do. Arise, let us go hence.",
    "options": [
      "Am in",
      "Am",
      "Love",
      "Know"
    ],
    "answer": "Love",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "859a20b8-c64f-4267-9bec-d24bd44508ab",
    "reference": "13- John 15:3 \u201cYou are already clean because of the word spoken to you\u201d",
    "question": "Greater love hath no man than this, that a man __ his life for his friends.",
    "options": [
      "Sacrifice",
      "Submit",
      "Lay down",
      "Ignore"
    ],
    "answer": "Lay down",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ad92eef3-ca3c-46c2-aa89-892530ee6dc3",
    "reference": "14- Galatians 6:14 Boast only in the Cross of Jesus",
    "question": "Herein is my Father glorified, that ye __ much fruit; so shall ye be my disciples.",
    "options": [
      "Bear",
      "Enjoy",
      "Seek",
      "Bring"
    ],
    "answer": "Bear",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c04ec294-0a9d-4377-972d-0b086d22bdae",
    "reference": "14- Galatians 6:14 Boast only in the Cross of Jesus",
    "question": "For every man shall bear his own ___.",
    "options": [
      "Cross",
      "Burden",
      "Conscience",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Burden",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f1416800-52cf-46f0-9cfc-db5a4d1cbfe5",
    "reference": "14- Galatians 6:14 Boast only in the Cross of Jesus",
    "question": "If we live in the spirit, let us also walk in the ___.",
    "options": [
      "Spirit",
      "Lord",
      "Light",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "504efcf5-380d-4618-b9dd-e6f86ed00417",
    "reference": "15- Isaiah 54:17 \u201cNo weapon formed against you shall prosper\u201d",
    "question": "Can God be mocked?",
    "options": [
      "Sometimes",
      "Always",
      "No",
      "Maybe"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b7373c70-3ad2-40fb-b284-f3e2b841d45d",
    "reference": "15- Isaiah 54:17 \u201cNo weapon formed against you shall prosper\u201d",
    "question": "For a small moment have I forsaken thee; but with great __ will I gather thee.",
    "options": [
      "Power",
      "Mercies",
      "Unction",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Mercies",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cd6b4138-7421-4005-9fa9-248fdce00692",
    "reference": "15- Isaiah 54:17 \u201cNo weapon formed against you shall prosper\u201d",
    "question": "For the mountains shall depart, and the hills be removed; but my ___ shall not depart from thee, neither shall the covenant of my peace be removed, saith the Lord that hath mercy on thee.",
    "options": [
      "Kindness",
      "Love",
      "Blessing",
      "Favor"
    ],
    "answer": "Kindness",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e8fc5a74-c815-436e-92b8-ba70453e0565",
    "reference": "16- Romans 6:6 \u201cOur old man was crucified with [Christ]\u201d",
    "question": "Incline your ear, and come unto me: hear, and your soul shall __; and I will make an everlasting covenant with you, even the sure mercies of David.",
    "options": [
      "Be saved",
      "Survive",
      "Live",
      "Be redeemed"
    ],
    "answer": "Live",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7bfe2b60-3b74-4fb6-b22d-79a1c99b5a6c",
    "reference": "16- Romans 6:6 \u201cOur old man was crucified with [Christ]\u201d",
    "question": "What shall we say then? Shall we continue in ___, that grace may abound?",
    "options": [
      "Praise",
      "Sin",
      "Thanksgiving",
      "Ignorance"
    ],
    "answer": "Sin",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "160bda56-0d40-46fa-8311-261cc44e2ec7",
    "reference": "16- Romans 6:6 \u201cOur old man was crucified with [Christ]\u201d",
    "question": "Does death have dominion on Jesus?",
    "options": [
      "Absolutely",
      "No",
      "Maybe",
      "Not sure"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4d082f7f-71a9-4cc9-aaa7-fd16e5b05179",
    "reference": "17- Revelation 12:11 Overcoming the enemy by the Blood of the Lamb",
    "question": "For he that is dead is freed from ___.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Punishment",
      "Sin",
      "Commandment"
    ],
    "answer": "Sin",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "eecb18e8-540d-4311-a16c-ca13e748c711",
    "reference": "17- Revelation 12:11 Overcoming the enemy by the Blood of the Lamb",
    "question": "What is another name of Satan?",
    "options": [
      "Devil",
      "Old serpent",
      "Dragon",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f3fb0339-c702-4fa7-957c-c89b2da8ef1e",
    "reference": "17- Revelation 12:11 Overcoming the enemy by the Blood of the Lamb",
    "question": "If any man have an ear, let him ___.",
    "options": [
      "Listen",
      "Hear",
      "Seek",
      "Know"
    ],
    "answer": "Hear",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "65f8bc42-4a6d-4916-836b-506002ed77e6",
    "reference": "18- James 4:7 \u201cSubmit to God; resist the devil\u201d",
    "question": "And they overcame him by the blood of the ___, and by the word of their testimony.",
    "options": [
      "Lamb",
      "Cow",
      "Chicken",
      "Bull"
    ],
    "answer": "Lamb",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "55a582b9-05b4-44c8-972a-b7cdd1b906c2",
    "reference": "18- James 4:7 \u201cSubmit to God; resist the devil\u201d",
    "question": "Ye ask, and receive not, because ye ask amiss, that ye may ___ it upon your lusts.",
    "options": [
      "Consume",
      "Bring",
      "Known",
      "Provide"
    ],
    "answer": "Consume",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "34bb331d-6d90-4c33-b141-0a7d0163cf42",
    "reference": "18- James 4:7 \u201cSubmit to God; resist the devil\u201d",
    "question": "___ yourselves in the sight of the Lord, and he shall lift you up.",
    "options": [
      "Rejoice",
      "Humble",
      "Bow",
      "Clean"
    ],
    "answer": "Humble",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d0dd09a7-74f3-4692-9dbb-288addf2a43d",
    "reference": "19- Philippians 4:19 \u201cGod shall supply all your need\u201d",
    "question": "But now ye rejoice in your boastings: all such rejoicing is ___.",
    "options": [
      "Evil",
      "Shameful",
      "Disrespectful",
      "Bad"
    ],
    "answer": "Evil",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fc3faae8-963b-4ba7-82f5-04d09bf5e300",
    "reference": "19- Philippians 4:19 \u201cGod shall supply all your need\u201d",
    "question": "I can do ___ things through Christ which strengtheneth me.",
    "options": [
      "Some",
      "All",
      "Miraculous",
      "Wonderful"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "867258b3-cd6b-40a7-84ba-75c71e43b750",
    "reference": "19- Philippians 4:19 \u201cGod shall supply all your need\u201d",
    "question": "And the peace of God, which passeth all understanding, shall keep your __ and minds through Christ Jesus.",
    "options": [
      "Nations",
      "Hearts",
      "Country",
      "Neighborhood"
    ],
    "answer": "Hearts",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6984b310-3265-4887-a95d-b1d1b22f6d84",
    "reference": "20- 1 John 4:4 \u201cHe who is in you is greater than he who is in the world\u201d",
    "question": "Then saith he unto his disciples, The harvest truly is plenteous, but the ____ are few;",
    "options": [
      "Workers",
      "Believers",
      "Sinners",
      "Laborers"
    ],
    "answer": "Laborers",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a91b4f96-d3d2-4ee5-915f-49961b235fcc",
    "reference": "20- 1 John 4:4 \u201cHe who is in you is greater than he who is in the world\u201d",
    "question": "And whatsoever we ask, we receive of him, because we keep his ___, and to those things that are pleasing in his sight.",
    "options": [
      "Commandments",
      "Law",
      "Principles",
      "Love"
    ],
    "answer": "Commandments",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "390eb29e-a2f9-4f9a-af3e-14b36dba1a00",
    "reference": "20- 1 John 4:4 \u201cHe who is in you is greater than he who is in the world\u201d",
    "question": "Beloved, let us love one another: for love is of ___; and every one that loveth is born of God, and knoweth God.",
    "options": [
      "Christ",
      "God",
      "Believers",
      "The world"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "67d0c170-4d0f-4e41-84b4-a7460ca9a364",
    "reference": "21- Proverbs 4:10 \u201cHear \u2026 and receive my sayings, and the years of your life will be many\u201d",
    "question": "We love him, because he __ loved us.",
    "options": [
      "Always",
      "First",
      "Sometimes",
      "Never"
    ],
    "answer": "First",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e77444d4-2943-48d3-8d62-8c69d1d23692",
    "reference": "21- Proverbs 4:10 \u201cHear \u2026 and receive my sayings, and the years of your life will be many\u201d",
    "question": "For I give you good ____, forsake ye not my law.",
    "options": [
      "Wisdom",
      "Doctrine",
      "Blessing",
      "Affection"
    ],
    "answer": "Doctrine",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2590faa6-1546-43c5-940c-bdfcd41abcc6",
    "reference": "21- Proverbs 4:10 \u201cHear \u2026 and receive my sayings, and the years of your life will be many\u201d",
    "question": "According to Proverbs 4, what is the principal thing?",
    "options": [
      "Understanding",
      "Love",
      "Wisdom",
      "Knowledge"
    ],
    "answer": "Wisdom",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0d61759c-8832-4f7a-8a07-1ad7e43321a3",
    "reference": "22- Ecclesiastes 12:13 Man\u2019s Whole Duty is to Fear God",
    "question": "What must we take fast hold of?",
    "options": [
      "Instruction",
      "Discipline",
      "Wisdom",
      "Knowledge"
    ],
    "answer": "Instruction",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8c51171a-c0dd-4ef0-96bb-94d2e70fc29d",
    "reference": "22- Ecclesiastes 12:13 Man\u2019s Whole Duty is to Fear God",
    "question": "What is the whole duty of Man?",
    "options": [
      "Praise God",
      "Fear God",
      "Follow God",
      "Love God"
    ],
    "answer": "Fear God",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "faa7b185-7379-41e6-974e-45b233fe02bf",
    "reference": "22- Ecclesiastes 12:13 Man\u2019s Whole Duty is to Fear God",
    "question": "When must we remember our Creator?",
    "options": [
      "Anytime",
      "Occasionally",
      "Never",
      "In the days of our youth"
    ],
    "answer": "In the days of our youth",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d74ac92e-91bf-4886-a7f1-96525a3ac166",
    "reference": "23- Ecclesiastes 3: 1-8 There is Time for Everything",
    "question": "What can the words of the wise be compared to?",
    "options": [
      "Jewels",
      "Honey",
      "Goads",
      "Golds"
    ],
    "answer": "Goads",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "900db0db-51f1-414a-934f-e45f4093a0f0",
    "reference": "23- Ecclesiastes 3: 1-8 There is Time for Everything",
    "question": "According to Ecclesiastes 3, which of these times come first; 'time to speak', 'time to keep silent'?",
    "options": [
      "Time to keep silent",
      "Time to speak",
      "None is first",
      "Both come at the same time"
    ],
    "answer": "Time to keep silent",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fdfe72bb-a588-4ff5-a36b-a10670c6430f",
    "reference": "23- Ecclesiastes 3: 1-8 There is Time for Everything",
    "question": "What does God give to a man that is good in his sight?",
    "options": [
      "Wisdom",
      "Knowledge",
      "Joy",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f24c4e5c-bc93-4dcc-858a-0246987efce8",
    "reference": "24- Lamentations 3:24 \u201cThe LORD is my portion\u201d",
    "question": "Why should every man eat and drink, and enjoy the good of all his labor?",
    "options": [
      "It's the Lord will",
      "It's gain through his hard work",
      "It's the gift of God",
      "It's an obligation"
    ],
    "answer": "It's the gift of God",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7dcbd45f-71e1-4a1f-9a78-d4e5aa756ead",
    "reference": "24- Lamentations 3:24 \u201cThe LORD is my portion\u201d",
    "question": "Why would you hope in the LORD?",
    "options": [
      "Because he is the king",
      "Because he loves you",
      "Because he requires so",
      "Because he is your portion"
    ],
    "answer": "Because he is your portion",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b54324b2-1368-45e1-b57e-1b63cf4d243e",
    "reference": "24- Lamentations 3:24 \u201cThe LORD is my portion\u201d",
    "question": "Why are we not consumed?",
    "options": [
      "Because of the Lord's mercies",
      "Because of sin no more",
      "Because we are more than conquerors",
      "Because we are powerful"
    ],
    "answer": "Because of the Lord's mercies",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "57ac747b-d1ea-4b19-92dd-9329aeb1f190",
    "reference": "25- Isaiah 54:4 \u201cDo not fear, for you will not be ashamed\u201d",
    "question": "Let us lift up our ___ with our hands unto God in the heavens.",
    "options": [
      "Remembrance",
      "Recognition",
      "Heart",
      "Praise"
    ],
    "answer": "Heart",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b303ad7e-2c0d-4757-bd75-0323f6e4e542",
    "reference": "25- Isaiah 54:4 \u201cDo not fear, for you will not be ashamed\u201d",
    "question": "Why was Jesus wounded?",
    "options": [
      "For his sins",
      "For his disobedience",
      "For our transgressions",
      "To show us love"
    ],
    "answer": "For our transgressions",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9cbb4373-42e4-4d45-b9c7-e7bf6cce7610",
    "reference": "25- Isaiah 54:4 \u201cDo not fear, for you will not be ashamed\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the husband of the widows?",
    "options": [
      "Nobody",
      "They have no husbands",
      "The Lord",
      "Their brother-in law"
    ],
    "answer": "The Lord",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ab8843dd-7173-424a-a486-1b2192d4dce6",
    "reference": "26- Ecclesiastes 12:14 \u201cGod will bring every work into judgment\u201d",
    "question": "For a small moment have I forsaken thee; but with great ___ will I gather thee.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Mercies",
      "Power",
      "Compassion"
    ],
    "answer": "Mercies",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2a6d871b-c18a-46d4-8da9-cf75e8765a75",
    "reference": "26- Ecclesiastes 12:14 \u201cGod will bring every work into judgment\u201d",
    "question": "What is the whole duty of man?",
    "options": [
      "Fear God",
      "Preach the gospel",
      "Worship God",
      "Donate to charities"
    ],
    "answer": "Fear God",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2117eab1-0014-4e6f-aa5f-5a95aeafdbd7",
    "reference": "26- Ecclesiastes 12:14 \u201cGod will bring every work into judgment\u201d",
    "question": "What did the preacher teach people?",
    "options": [
      "The word",
      "Wisdom",
      "Knowledge",
      "Songs"
    ],
    "answer": "Knowledge",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d05a5ad3-6ed0-400e-bd7e-ca510ffb635a",
    "reference": "27- Mark 11:22-25 Principles of Asking and Receiving",
    "question": "Where shall the dust return to?",
    "options": [
      "God",
      "The sea",
      "The river",
      "The earth"
    ],
    "answer": "The earth",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bad2d7db-8032-4b42-a06f-97e550c26967",
    "reference": "27- Mark 11:22-25 Principles of Asking and Receiving",
    "question": "What did Jesus ask his disciples to have?",
    "options": [
      "Faith",
      "Love",
      "Perseverance",
      "Hope"
    ],
    "answer": "Faith",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ae1794a7-119c-4737-b400-0505933200d3",
    "reference": "27- Mark 11:22-25 Principles of Asking and Receiving",
    "question": "How can we make sure that we receive what we ask in prayers?",
    "options": [
      "Pray without ceasing",
      "Pray only when necessary",
      "Believe in what we are praying for",
      "Trust God"
    ],
    "answer": "Believe in what we are praying for",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e8610e7d-92f4-4d9a-881e-47245dda0171",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 127:1 \u201cUnless the LORD builds the house, they labor in vain\u201d",
    "question": "What happens if we do not forgive others?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "Bad things",
      "Judgment",
      "God will not forgive us also"
    ],
    "answer": "God will not forgive us also",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1e792828-9edc-44f7-97bb-97ed804e6841",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 127:1 \u201cUnless the LORD builds the house, they labor in vain\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord hath done great things for us; wherefore we are ___.",
    "options": [
      "Privileged",
      "Blessed",
      "Glad",
      "Saved"
    ],
    "answer": "Glad",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7f438dbc-9f76-4d39-993d-502d5e2b2016",
    "reference": "28- Psalm 127:1 \u201cUnless the LORD builds the house, they labor in vain\u201d",
    "question": "What are children?",
    "options": [
      "Heritage",
      "As arrows",
      "Fruit",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "699abf3f-1926-43e0-997c-b024de02ebf0",
    "reference": "29- John 14:16 God the Father Will Give You the Holy Spirit as a Helper",
    "question": "Who gives the fruit of the womb?",
    "options": [
      "Fathers",
      "Mothers",
      "God",
      "Pastors"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5188aea9-0db8-4807-9054-2185f61f0e51",
    "reference": "29- John 14:16 God the Father Will Give You the Holy Spirit as a Helper",
    "question": "Who said to the Lord that they did not know where he (the Lord) is going?",
    "options": [
      "Thomas",
      "Peter",
      "Paul",
      "Judas"
    ],
    "answer": "Thomas",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "82b60fb9-50ea-46a4-8774-a089d5c0bb77",
    "reference": "29- John 14:16 God the Father Will Give You the Holy Spirit as a Helper",
    "question": "What can be asked in the name of Jesus?",
    "options": [
      "Grace",
      "Gifts",
      "Any thing",
      "Salvation"
    ],
    "answer": "Any thing",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "58dea037-e56f-449a-9dd8-ecb21f1af292",
    "reference": "29- John 14:16 God the Father Will Give You the Holy Spirit as a Helper",
    "question": "Who is the Holy Spirit?",
    "options": [
      "The Comforter",
      "The Spirit of truth",
      "Jesus",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1c3f2b5b-d6c2-483e-9178-cba54b74c77d",
    "reference": "30- Psalm 16:11 \u201cYou will show me the path of life\u201d",
    "question": "Why can't the world receive the Holy Spirit?",
    "options": [
      "Because he is not real",
      "Because they can't see him",
      "Because they don't know him",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "80ab986f-3aa7-4774-ac48-d89d0e6f3d10",
    "reference": "30- Psalm 16:11 \u201cYou will show me the path of life\u201d",
    "question": "What happens in the presence of the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "There is fullness of joy",
      "There is love",
      "There is wisdom",
      "There is grace"
    ],
    "answer": "There is fullness of joy",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fbda76ba-376c-4275-9171-ab0cb8d440ae",
    "reference": "30- Psalm 16:11 \u201cYou will show me the path of life\u201d",
    "question": "The Lord is the portion of mine ___ and of my cup: thou maintainest my lot.",
    "options": [
      "Riches",
      "Wisdom",
      "Inheritance",
      "Household"
    ],
    "answer": "Inheritance",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ecf416df-ba81-48a6-9725-ee33da1809a2",
    "reference": "30- Psalm 16:11 \u201cYou will show me the path of life\u201d",
    "question": "What will happen to those who seek after other gods?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "They'll regret it",
      "They'll be forgiven",
      "Their sorrows will be multiplied"
    ],
    "answer": "Their sorrows will be multiplied",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9cb85cbf-e5e6-426a-8424-e972f8541c30",
    "reference": "1- Isaiah 54:10 \u201cNor shall My covenant of peace be removed\u201d",
    "question": "Who is Isaiah 54 is addressed to?",
    "options": [
      "Women",
      "Married Women",
      "Barren Women",
      "Believers"
    ],
    "answer": "Barren Women",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c9cc623a-ea5a-44dc-a65a-be12524585d6",
    "reference": "1- Isaiah 54:10 \u201cNor shall My covenant of peace be removed\u201d",
    "question": "Who shall the children be taught of?",
    "options": [
      "Moses",
      "Isaiah",
      "Abraham",
      "The Lord"
    ],
    "answer": "The Lord",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "376f09be-8734-48bd-9856-9e526f0b3308",
    "reference": "2- Proverbs 6:2 \u201cYou are snared by the words of your mouth\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the husband of the widower?",
    "options": [
      "The Lord of hosts",
      "The Holy One",
      "Her Maker",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d63fadac-be98-4a38-ae1a-deac65f700f0",
    "reference": "2- Proverbs 6:2 \u201cYou are snared by the words of your mouth\u201d",
    "question": "For the ways of man are ___ the eyes of the Lord, and he pondereth all his goings.",
    "options": [
      "Guided by",
      "Known",
      "Before",
      "Seen by"
    ],
    "answer": "Before",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2ecab957-6d61-4a16-8a10-69e80718e893",
    "reference": "2- Proverbs 6:2 \u201cYou are snared by the words of your mouth\u201d",
    "question": "Who are we recommended to learn from?",
    "options": [
      "God",
      "Jesus",
      "Our friends",
      "Ant"
    ],
    "answer": "Ant",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3a925907-f6fc-4c89-a12b-664a4a3fa8ed",
    "reference": "3- Psalm 9:7 \u201cThe LORD shall endure forever\u201d",
    "question": "According to Proverbs 6, what happens to the one who sleeps or fold his/her hands?",
    "options": [
      "They'll gain weights",
      "They'll see vision",
      "They'll face poverty",
      "They'll be used by the Lord mightily"
    ],
    "answer": "They'll face poverty",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a8b5ce1e-d9df-4448-99aa-63666b78d85f",
    "reference": "3- Psalm 9:7 \u201cThe LORD shall endure forever\u201d",
    "question": "What will happen to your enemies if you trust in the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "They will fall",
      "Nothing",
      "They will perish",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "a & c",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "96920125-72a5-49fc-a0a6-7bed5f03178d",
    "reference": "3- Psalm 9:7 \u201cThe LORD shall endure forever\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the refuge of the oppressed?",
    "options": [
      "The Lord",
      "The government",
      "Their family",
      "No-one"
    ],
    "answer": "The Lord",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "18374339-7b57-405d-9a62-178181baae96",
    "reference": "4- Psalm 77:12 \u201cI will also meditate on all Your work\u201d",
    "question": "What is the Lord known by?",
    "options": [
      "His name",
      "His mighty deeds",
      "His love",
      "His judgment"
    ],
    "answer": "His judgment",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9824e42d-a805-4077-9b1b-f6a05f8da008",
    "reference": "4- Psalm 77:12 \u201cI will also meditate on all Your work\u201d",
    "question": "What is the way of God?",
    "options": [
      "Peaceful",
      "Great",
      "The sanctuary",
      "Cursed"
    ],
    "answer": "The sanctuary",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b36aeac9-fced-40d4-b851-3e54c58d72ad",
    "reference": "4- Psalm 77:12 \u201cI will also meditate on all Your work\u201d",
    "question": "According to Psalm 77 who lead the way of God children?",
    "options": [
      "Jesus",
      "Aaron",
      "Moses",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "85bd98cf-c5c3-4df5-b109-e3eee9817cdf",
    "reference": "5- Psalm 103:12 \u201cHe removed our transgressions from us\u201d",
    "question": "How is the Lord to the kings of the earth?",
    "options": [
      "Kind",
      "Gentle",
      "Terrible",
      "Compassionate"
    ],
    "answer": "Terrible",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a8beac77-d322-4f22-9a75-8fca7f0d4366",
    "reference": "5- Psalm 103:12 \u201cHe removed our transgressions from us\u201d",
    "question": "Which of these does the Lord cover his children with?",
    "options": [
      "Clothes",
      "Tender mercies",
      "Lovingkindness",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8e47b45d-7d4a-46cd-9816-8c442ec3b572",
    "reference": "5- Psalm 103:12 \u201cHe removed our transgressions from us\u201d",
    "question": "How is the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "Merciful",
      "Gracious",
      "Slow to anger",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "625f27a8-3d94-4b83-a493-88d03da2b6c0",
    "reference": "6- Joel 2:12-13 \u201cTurn to Me with all your heart\u201d",
    "question": "Who does the Lord has pitied on?",
    "options": [
      "His children",
      "Jesus",
      "Those who fear him",
      "Christians"
    ],
    "answer": "Those who fear him",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "40640874-3b2f-4c92-b1d0-6bccc6462210",
    "reference": "6- Joel 2:12-13 \u201cTurn to Me with all your heart\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Joel's father?",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Jacob",
      "Peter",
      "Pethuel"
    ],
    "answer": "Pethuel",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9960a1b2-617f-4557-8305-5ad24f7df0f9",
    "reference": "6- Joel 2:12-13 \u201cTurn to Me with all your heart\u201d",
    "question": "How is the Lord expecting his children to turn to him?",
    "options": [
      "With all their heart",
      "With fasting",
      "With weeping",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0cc4111c-6548-42a2-86b1-c11ba0c670b1",
    "reference": "7- Psalm 119:15 \u201cI will meditate on Your precepts\u201d",
    "question": "What did the Lord promise to send to his children after repentance?",
    "options": [
      "Oil",
      "Wine",
      "Corn",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "633085d5-79c6-4cd0-bae4-f9d51707c9f9",
    "reference": "7- Psalm 119:15 \u201cI will meditate on Your precepts\u201d",
    "question": "Why must we hid God word in our heart?",
    "options": [
      "So that we remember it",
      "So that we may proclaim it",
      "So that we might not sin",
      "So that we might have eternal life"
    ],
    "answer": "So that we might not sin",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f4c850d8-c32e-480d-8fad-69ea2dcbeb0d",
    "reference": "7- Psalm 119:15 \u201cI will meditate on Your precepts\u201d",
    "question": "Who does the Lord rebuke?",
    "options": [
      "The kind",
      "The meek",
      "The proud",
      "The Israelite"
    ],
    "answer": "The proud",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9478ed06-2701-43f0-b02d-2858c4790427",
    "reference": "8- Romans 5:8 \u201cWhile we were still sinners Christ died for us\u201d",
    "question": "Blessed are they that keep his ____, and that seek him with the whole heart.",
    "options": [
      "Ways",
      "Testimonies",
      "Commandment",
      "Love"
    ],
    "answer": "Testimonies",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f2497b37-f2cb-4f24-a364-b224d16d269f",
    "reference": "8- Romans 5:8 \u201cWhile we were still sinners Christ died for us\u201d",
    "question": "How have Christians been justified?",
    "options": [
      "Through love",
      "Through faith",
      "Through resurrection",
      "Through hope"
    ],
    "answer": "Through faith",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "70d4b4ad-4ebc-447d-b14d-ac485167cbfc",
    "reference": "8- Romans 5:8 \u201cWhile we were still sinners Christ died for us\u201d",
    "question": "How does God demonstrate his love for us?",
    "options": [
      "Through the death of Christ",
      "Through many gifts",
      "Through his compassion",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Through the death of Christ",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "edca4bf3-356b-4349-8cf8-dd6309a45ec3",
    "reference": "9- 2 Timothy 2:3-7 \u201cMay the Lord give you understanding in all things\u201d",
    "question": "What does suffering produce?",
    "options": [
      "Fear",
      "Perseverance",
      "Experience",
      "Hope"
    ],
    "answer": "Perseverance",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "98185186-d333-476c-bb9d-0c4b2bce995c",
    "reference": "9- 2 Timothy 2:3-7 \u201cMay the Lord give you understanding in all things\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the author of 2 Timothy?",
    "options": [
      "Timothy",
      "John",
      "Peter",
      "Paul"
    ],
    "answer": "Paul",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "72f370ab-85ab-4d65-9285-4a85c41ea5ad",
    "reference": "9- 2 Timothy 2:3-7 \u201cMay the Lord give you understanding in all things\u201d",
    "question": "Thou therefore endure ___ as a good soldier of Jesus Christ",
    "options": [
      "Gifts",
      "Supply",
      "Love",
      "Hardness"
    ],
    "answer": "Hardness",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "147b4805-30a9-4b52-ae19-21f2edcdaaf6",
    "reference": "10- Revelation 3:5 \u201cHe who overcomes shall be clothed in white garments\u201d",
    "question": "If we suffer, we shall also ___ with him: if we deny him, he also will deny us.",
    "options": [
      "Rejoice",
      "Hope",
      "Reign",
      "Lead"
    ],
    "answer": "Reign",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bc0bfad0-23ef-45f6-9c4d-07b270444fcc",
    "reference": "10- Revelation 3:5 \u201cHe who overcomes shall be clothed in white garments\u201d",
    "question": "Which book comes immediately before Revelation?",
    "options": [
      "1 John",
      "John",
      "Jude",
      "3 John"
    ],
    "answer": "Jude",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b42920ac-dc18-4d60-ba8b-4d0fb47d5793",
    "reference": "10- Revelation 3:5 \u201cHe who overcomes shall be clothed in white garments\u201d",
    "question": "How will Jesus come like?",
    "options": [
      "A thief",
      "A prince",
      "An angel",
      "A lion"
    ],
    "answer": "A thief",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2cd35a9b-6491-485d-9f3c-1f751a1227a8",
    "reference": "11- Matthew 6:26-31 God Cares for Our Well-being",
    "question": "What will happen to those who are victorious?",
    "options": [
      "They will see God",
      "They will receive rewards",
      "Their names will never be removed from the book of life",
      "They will reign forever"
    ],
    "answer": "Their names will never be removed from the book of life",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "840f7cfd-e4bb-4a49-9b26-6ef3b573c00f",
    "reference": "11- Matthew 6:26-31 God Cares for Our Well-being",
    "question": "Who feed the birds of the earth?",
    "options": [
      "They feed themselves",
      "The passerby",
      "God",
      "Nobody"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6d4e8921-8656-47b6-8012-8929717c0935",
    "reference": "11- Matthew 6:26-31 God Cares for Our Well-being",
    "question": "Who can serve two masters?",
    "options": [
      "Jesus",
      "Unbelievers",
      "No-one",
      "Priests"
    ],
    "answer": "No-one",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ca104129-a7fe-4643-945c-e4a78276b020",
    "reference": "12- Matthew 6:33 \u201cSeek first the kingdom of God\u201d",
    "question": "What must Christians worry about?",
    "options": [
      "Their children",
      "Their money",
      "Their health",
      "Nothing"
    ],
    "answer": "Nothing",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0fa2f78e-2d04-4851-9e9e-f7b63d5040b2",
    "reference": "12- Matthew 6:33 \u201cSeek first the kingdom of God\u201d",
    "question": "What happens if you make the kingdom of God your priority?",
    "options": [
      "God will remember you",
      "God will visit you",
      "God will provide all you need",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "God will provide all you need",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "819c82ce-0199-4fa3-b975-223a3b66ac0d",
    "reference": "12- Matthew 6:33 \u201cSeek first the kingdom of God\u201d",
    "question": "Why must you not worry about tomorrow?",
    "options": [
      "Because it is the future",
      "Because God hasn't promise us tomorrow",
      "Because tomorrow will worry about itself",
      "Because it doesn't make sense"
    ],
    "answer": "Because tomorrow will worry about itself",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "34019c05-90c3-474c-8e5f-f86541d78244",
    "reference": "13- Matthew 16:19 \u201cI will give you the keys of the kingdom of heaven\u201d",
    "question": "Where must we store our treasures?",
    "options": [
      "Here on earth",
      "In the bank",
      "Under the bed",
      "In heaven"
    ],
    "answer": "In heaven",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f52d0b97-2dd6-486c-8c44-f1b7f09a587e",
    "reference": "13- Matthew 16:19 \u201cI will give you the keys of the kingdom of heaven\u201d",
    "question": "To whom did Jesus say you are the rock?",
    "options": [
      "Judas",
      "Jeremiah",
      "Paul",
      "Peter"
    ],
    "answer": "Peter",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "770373ba-8a74-46b6-bf0d-21d16d310030",
    "reference": "13- Matthew 16:19 \u201cI will give you the keys of the kingdom of heaven\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Simon's father?",
    "options": [
      "Jonah",
      "Abraham",
      "Jacob",
      "Jesus"
    ],
    "answer": "Jonah",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6eef97e0-2cd3-4a67-84aa-f62938c1501d",
    "reference": "14- Galatians 1:4 Christ Gave Himself to Deliver Us from Evil",
    "question": "Why did Jesus rebuke Peter?",
    "options": [
      "He didn't",
      "Because Peter said Jesus will not suffer",
      "Because Peter asked stupid questions",
      "Because Peter was uncleaned"
    ],
    "answer": "Because Peter said Jesus will not suffer",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "abfb0e0d-e814-4f03-a4d1-ecbfdd2567fd",
    "reference": "14- Galatians 1:4 Christ Gave Himself to Deliver Us from Evil",
    "question": "Why did Jesus give himself?",
    "options": [
      "For love",
      "For compassion",
      "For our sins",
      "For our future"
    ],
    "answer": "For our sins",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4c61cb8c-2345-49e4-8c84-f4c675dffe76",
    "reference": "14- Galatians 1:4 Christ Gave Himself to Deliver Us from Evil",
    "question": "Why did Paul marvel?",
    "options": [
      "Because Galatians turned away from God",
      "Because he was not well received",
      "Because the offering was not enough",
      "Because the church was deserted"
    ],
    "answer": "Because Galatians turned away from God",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ca7e3d79-1176-47a3-957e-e266b8f00d5a",
    "reference": "15- James 1:22 \u201cBe doers of the word, and not hearers only\u201d",
    "question": "But I certify you, brethren, that the gospel which was ____ of me is not after man.",
    "options": [
      "Written",
      "Published",
      "Preached",
      "Spread"
    ],
    "answer": "Preached",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4973bd2d-4fa9-4cf0-b846-39617ef68e93",
    "reference": "15- James 1:22 \u201cBe doers of the word, and not hearers only\u201d",
    "question": "Which of these attitudes is recommended by James?",
    "options": [
      "Slow to become angry",
      "Slow to speak",
      "Quick to listen",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3bb20c45-8427-48ec-84d0-93312a647488",
    "reference": "15- James 1:22 \u201cBe doers of the word, and not hearers only\u201d",
    "question": "Can we be tempted by God?",
    "options": [
      "Absolutely",
      "Occasionally",
      "No",
      "Maybe"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3256ecd1-76b0-4e8b-a9a1-979500b111c4",
    "reference": "16- Philippians 4:7 \u201cThe peace of God \u2026 will guard your hearts and minds\u201d",
    "question": "According to James what does the testing of our faith produce?",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Compassion",
      "Ambition",
      "Perseverance"
    ],
    "answer": "Perseverance",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "52d74a6f-e7e4-4bf7-a754-6af9a3964bc9",
    "reference": "16- Philippians 4:7 \u201cThe peace of God \u2026 will guard your hearts and minds\u201d",
    "question": "Who is Paul pleading with, to have the same mind?",
    "options": [
      "Euodia & Syntyche",
      "Euodia & Clement",
      "Clement & Syntyche",
      "Clement & Timothy"
    ],
    "answer": "Euodia & Syntyche",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "630f46f9-463c-4fde-af7b-ae169615e219",
    "reference": "16- Philippians 4:7 \u201cThe peace of God \u2026 will guard your hearts and minds\u201d",
    "question": "What is Paul recommending Philippians to put in practice?",
    "options": [
      "What they've learned from him",
      "What they've heard from him",
      "What they've seen in him",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ccff41c8-a13d-4162-b5fa-354719c78c0c",
    "reference": "17- Habakkuk 2:4 \u201cThe just shall live by his faith\u201d",
    "question": "What must we be careful about?",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Money",
      "Nothing",
      "Security"
    ],
    "answer": "Nothing",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "174306e9-51a5-48f6-8acf-3bbc26470c18",
    "reference": "17- Habakkuk 2:4 \u201cThe just shall live by his faith\u201d",
    "question": "Where did the Lord ask Habakkuk to write the vision on?",
    "options": [
      "His heart",
      "Nonperishable papers",
      "Tables",
      "It is not clear"
    ],
    "answer": "Tables",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ba095caa-c2ab-4433-b80c-c1d0236581cb",
    "reference": "17- Habakkuk 2:4 \u201cThe just shall live by his faith\u201d",
    "question": "When is the vision for?",
    "options": [
      "Everlasting",
      "Every day",
      "An appointed time",
      "The future"
    ],
    "answer": "An appointed time",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7e86cf56-2308-4168-9fd5-9eedabc2c1bc",
    "reference": "18- Proverbs 28:13 \u201cHe who covers his sins will not prosper\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Habakkuk?",
    "options": [
      "A preacher",
      "A teacher",
      "A dreamer",
      "A prophet"
    ],
    "answer": "A prophet",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ce523df7-4751-42d3-8084-c8bf7ed7bf9a",
    "reference": "18- Proverbs 28:13 \u201cHe who covers his sins will not prosper\u201d",
    "question": "What is a poor man that oppressed the poor compare to?",
    "options": [
      "A fool",
      "A wise",
      "A sweeping rain which leaves no food",
      "a & c"
    ],
    "answer": "A sweeping rain which leaves no food",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f1489db9-0237-41f9-81b2-0223d8087fe8",
    "reference": "18- Proverbs 28:13 \u201cHe who covers his sins will not prosper\u201d",
    "question": "What happens to the prayer of those that turn away their ear from hearing the law?",
    "options": [
      "Unanswered",
      "Ignored",
      "Answered",
      "Abomination"
    ],
    "answer": "Abomination",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0b573103-c796-4c6b-ad92-edad82bc71ce",
    "reference": "19- Psalm 19:14 \u201cLet the words of my mouth and the meditation of my heart be acceptable in Your sight\u201d",
    "question": "The wicked flee when no man pursueth: but the righteous are ___ as a lion.",
    "options": [
      "Wise",
      "Bold",
      "Fearless",
      "Courageous"
    ],
    "answer": "Bold",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cf6f1155-d8f2-497a-91f4-315a11edf02a",
    "reference": "19- Psalm 19:14 \u201cLet the words of my mouth and the meditation of my heart be acceptable in Your sight\u201d",
    "question": "How is the law of the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "Perfect",
      "Difficult",
      "Unbearable",
      "Good"
    ],
    "answer": "Perfect",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0c5689ec-392d-4336-b206-90dafb2514d2",
    "reference": "20- Deuteronomy 8:18 \u201cIt is [God] who gives you power to get wealth\u201d",
    "question": "How are the judgments of the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "Good",
      "True",
      "Righteous",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b94ce8ff-5783-447c-bb55-6b5c67fa9c6f",
    "reference": "20- Deuteronomy 8:18 \u201cIt is [God] who gives you power to get wealth\u201d",
    "question": "Which of the commandments shall be observed?",
    "options": [
      "Any",
      "Some",
      "All",
      "None"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b7456592-a1b4-48cb-9390-4891ddb3d33c",
    "reference": "20- Deuteronomy 8:18 \u201cIt is [God] who gives you power to get wealth\u201d",
    "question": "For the Lord thy God bringeth thee into a __ land, a land of brooks of water, of fountains and depths that spring out of valleys and hills.",
    "options": [
      "Good",
      "Prosperous",
      "Blessed",
      "Desolated"
    ],
    "answer": "Good",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cc4eae8a-73d9-4397-bdd0-cf115fdf0bf9",
    "reference": "21- Psalm 63:5 \u201cMy soul shall be satisfied\u201d",
    "question": "Who gives you the power to get wealth?",
    "options": [
      "The government",
      "Your hard-work",
      "The society",
      "God"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "76e4ab2d-4d25-4c91-a0f6-caa039b84062",
    "reference": "21- Psalm 63:5 \u201cMy soul shall be satisfied\u201d",
    "question": "Who does power belong to?",
    "options": [
      "The government",
      "Satan",
      "God",
      "Unbelievers"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1223c6aa-93b3-408d-9888-b1b75384fd3f",
    "reference": "21- Psalm 63:5 \u201cMy soul shall be satisfied\u201d",
    "question": "Thus will I ___ thee while I live: I will lift up my hands in thy name.",
    "options": [
      "Praise",
      "Worship",
      "Bless",
      "Seek"
    ],
    "answer": "Bless",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2d3f9e04-d0d2-4807-a6d0-1ba545589292",
    "reference": "22- Proverbs 13:22 God Stores the Sinner\u2019s Wealth for the Righteous",
    "question": "Also unto thee, O Lord, belongeth __: for thou renderest to every man according to his work.",
    "options": [
      "Mercy",
      "Power",
      "Life",
      "Peace"
    ],
    "answer": "Mercy",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3f703ab4-c908-4c0f-a964-d9fc92a0ef52",
    "reference": "22- Proverbs 13:22 God Stores the Sinner\u2019s Wealth for the Righteous",
    "question": "What does a good man do?",
    "options": [
      "Serves the Lord",
      "Give to charity",
      "Leaves an inheritance to his children",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Leaves an inheritance to his children",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "79e9735b-7068-4171-bd7e-7b29654a661b",
    "reference": "22- Proverbs 13:22 God Stores the Sinner\u2019s Wealth for the Righteous",
    "question": "What awaits those who despise the word?",
    "options": [
      "Nothing",
      "Calamity",
      "Destruction",
      "Help"
    ],
    "answer": "Destruction",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "55ab1456-e87c-4667-8438-555bf65d92ef",
    "reference": "23- Isaiah 49:7-9 \u201cI will preserve You and give You as a covenant to the people to restore the earth\u201d",
    "question": "What awaits those that refuse instruction?",
    "options": [
      "Calamity",
      "Shame",
      "Poverty",
      "b & c"
    ],
    "answer": "b & c",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f56e6100-3ec7-42cf-8711-87c510c3b6d4",
    "reference": "23- Isaiah 49:7-9 \u201cI will preserve You and give You as a covenant to the people to restore the earth\u201d",
    "question": "And said unto me, thou art my servant, O Israel, in whom I will be ___.",
    "options": [
      "Known",
      "Glorified",
      "Revealed",
      "Concealed"
    ],
    "answer": "Glorified",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3cf82c09-6352-4e20-aecb-40cf736f0944",
    "reference": "24- 2 Peter 2:9 God delivers the Godly from Temptations",
    "question": "Why must we shout for joy, and rejoice?",
    "options": [
      "Because the Lord comforts his people",
      "Because the Lord will have compassion on the afflicted",
      "Because it is wise to do so",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "62b68f88-3956-4a22-acf9-858ae3b8ec09",
    "reference": "24- 2 Peter 2:9 God delivers the Godly from Temptations",
    "question": "Who was Peter?",
    "options": [
      "A teacher",
      "An apostle",
      "A deacon",
      "A priest"
    ],
    "answer": "An apostle",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1bc65224-1fc0-4f32-8248-89473b10080d",
    "reference": "25- Deuteronomy 31:6 \u201cBe strong and of good courage\u201d",
    "question": "How does prophecy come?",
    "options": [
      "By the Holy Ghost",
      "By faith",
      "By the will of men",
      "By practice"
    ],
    "answer": "By the Holy Ghost",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f648e673-2326-4959-9d5d-da566a5d39af",
    "reference": "25- Deuteronomy 31:6 \u201cBe strong and of good courage\u201d",
    "question": "Why must we not be afraid?",
    "options": [
      "Because the Lord is with us",
      "Because fear is not real",
      "Because there is nothing to be afraid of",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Because the Lord is with us",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cf6943a8-ed1a-4112-a8fb-5b502f28bcaa",
    "reference": "25- Deuteronomy 31:6 \u201cBe strong and of good courage\u201d",
    "question": "Who carried the ark of covenant?",
    "options": [
      "Moses",
      "Joshua",
      "The Levitical priests",
      "Jacob"
    ],
    "answer": "The Levitical priests",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b6a0b540-c2cd-4960-9055-c8f5494800d4",
    "reference": "26- Ephesians 5:19-20 \u201cSinging and making melody \u2026 to the Lord\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Joshua's father?",
    "options": [
      "Nun",
      "Peter",
      "Moses",
      "Jacob"
    ],
    "answer": "Nun",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "53d47bf9-91da-4fc6-b0bd-1f89dc139c85",
    "reference": "26- Ephesians 5:19-20 \u201cSinging and making melody \u2026 to the Lord\u201d",
    "question": "And walk in ___, as Christ also hath loved us, and hath given himself for us an offering and a sacrifice to God for a sweetsmelling savor.",
    "options": [
      "Understanding",
      "Love",
      "Harmony",
      "Faith"
    ],
    "answer": "Love",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "38dd4384-a57a-47ab-8602-93574151cb7b",
    "reference": "26- Ephesians 5:19-20 \u201cSinging and making melody \u2026 to the Lord\u201d",
    "question": "And have no ___ with the unfruitful works of darkness, but rather reprove them.",
    "options": [
      "Say",
      "Compassion",
      "Connection",
      "Fellowship"
    ],
    "answer": "Fellowship",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ed621907-0d84-499d-aeec-1d28536df9bf",
    "reference": "27- Ephesians 4:2 \u201cWith longsuffering, bearing with one another in love\u201d",
    "question": "When must \u2018we\u2019 Christians give thanks?",
    "options": [
      "When we feel like it",
      "Always",
      "Never",
      "If God called us"
    ],
    "answer": "Always",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e23cb58e-5e4d-44e1-8aa1-69f68549f28d",
    "reference": "27- Ephesians 4:2 \u201cWith longsuffering, bearing with one another in love\u201d",
    "question": "There is one body, and one ___, even as ye are called in one hope of your calling.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "God",
      "Spirit",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Spirit",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5d1a1721-d303-4990-8e43-b38348871bd3",
    "reference": "27- Ephesians 4:2 \u201cWith longsuffering, bearing with one another in love\u201d",
    "question": "This I say therefore, and testify in the Lord, that ye henceforth walk __ as other gentiles walk, in the vanity of their heart.",
    "options": [
      "Not",
      "Blindly",
      "Cowardly",
      "Helplessly"
    ],
    "answer": "Not",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "5008fb02-6e56-4cd0-b898-84dc4e756ce3",
    "reference": "28- 1 Peter 5:10 \u201cMay the God of all grace \u2026 strengthen and settle you\u201d",
    "question": "How are we saved?",
    "options": [
      "By obedience",
      "By longsuffering",
      "By works",
      "By grace"
    ],
    "answer": "By grace",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9675fa0e-b742-4307-a495-c1928503b851",
    "reference": "28- 1 Peter 5:10 \u201cMay the God of all grace \u2026 strengthen and settle you\u201d",
    "question": "According to 1 Peter 5, who will restore us?",
    "options": [
      "Jesus",
      "The word",
      "God himself",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "God himself",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "880f93e8-628f-4d86-a104-e5980c141014",
    "reference": "28- 1 Peter 5:10 \u201cMay the God of all grace \u2026 strengthen and settle you\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Peter?",
    "options": [
      "A preacher",
      "A teacher",
      "An apostle",
      "Jesus cousin"
    ],
    "answer": "An apostle",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8111dcfc-a6a8-4c90-a1fc-c531b4243ffc",
    "reference": "29- Luke 10:20 \u201cYour names are written in heaven\u201d",
    "question": "Casting all your care upon him; for he ___ for you.",
    "options": [
      "Beseech",
      "Careth",
      "Prays",
      "Plead"
    ],
    "answer": "Careth",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0e6e11d8-880b-4f39-83ab-e7dba2c17b34",
    "reference": "29- Luke 10:20 \u201cYour names are written in heaven\u201d",
    "question": "What is the purpose of the authority that has been given to believers?",
    "options": [
      "To trample on snakes",
      "To trample on scorpions",
      "To overcome all the power of the enemy",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All of the above",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1864b158-6a70-4ffe-868d-b722d5cbf081",
    "reference": "29- Luke 10:20 \u201cYour names are written in heaven\u201d",
    "question": "What has been committed to Jesus by God?",
    "options": [
      "All things",
      "The law",
      "The government",
      "The church"
    ],
    "answer": "All things",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "adfefdcd-0efe-4380-9073-5ef390c7b44e",
    "reference": "30- Matthew 11:28 \u201cCome to Me all you who labor and are heavy laden\u201d",
    "question": "And the seventy returned again with joy, saying Lord, even the ___ are subject unto us through thy name",
    "options": [
      "Wisdom",
      "World",
      "Devils",
      "Power"
    ],
    "answer": "Devils",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8798f8b5-a365-4dbf-8ded-506396502652",
    "reference": "30- Matthew 11:28 \u201cCome to Me all you who labor and are heavy laden\u201d",
    "question": "___ are delivered unto me of my Father: and no man knoweth the Son, but the Father; neither knoweth any man the Father, save the Son, and he to whomsoever the Son will reveal him.",
    "options": [
      "The worlds",
      "The devils",
      "Believers",
      "All things"
    ],
    "answer": "All things",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dadf9480-38ee-4ee6-bcca-0f0288ff8ac9",
    "reference": "30- Matthew 11:28 \u201cCome to Me all you who labor and are heavy laden\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the Lord of the Sabbath?",
    "options": [
      "Jesus",
      "The priest",
      "The government",
      "No-one"
    ],
    "answer": "Jesus",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b9c821ca-74b6-499f-aa6a-88ccf5c624e5",
    "reference": "31- Psalm 84:5-7 \u201cBlessed is the man whose strength is in you\u201d",
    "question": "He that findeth his life shall __ it: and he that loseth his life for my sake shall find it.",
    "options": [
      "Honor",
      "Lose",
      "Forget",
      "Find"
    ],
    "answer": "Lose",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "39011e81-4b5d-4640-8f9f-7c4c602b3cdc",
    "reference": "31- Psalm 84:5-7 \u201cBlessed is the man whose strength is in you\u201d",
    "question": "Blessed are they that ___ in thy house: they will be still praising thee.",
    "options": [
      "Come",
      "Visit",
      "Dwell",
      "Worship"
    ],
    "answer": "Dwell",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "25a5fa2c-a386-444e-b0ef-5be4da0fb46b",
    "reference": "31- Psalm 84:5-7 \u201cBlessed is the man whose strength is in you\u201d",
    "question": "O Lord of hosts, blessed is the man that ___ in thee.",
    "options": [
      "Sing",
      "Relieth",
      "Believeth",
      "Trusteth"
    ],
    "answer": "Trusteth",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "face2b59-4dbd-4809-abe3-03a4a57bbea1",
    "reference": "31- Psalm 84:5-7 \u201cBlessed is the man whose strength is in you\u201d",
    "question": "Thou hast forgiven the iniquity of thy people, thou hast covered ___ their sin.",
    "options": [
      "Some of",
      "All",
      "And clean",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dc5a095e-181c-4c06-a39a-843b6952759f",
    "reference": "1- Joshua 24:15 \u201cAs for me and my house, we will serve the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "Now therefore fear the Lord, and serve him in sincerity and in truth: and put away the __ which your fathers served on the other side of the flood, and in Egypt; and serve the Lord.",
    "options": [
      "Law",
      "Traditions",
      "Gods",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Gods",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bec09ce5-496f-4489-a47c-109e37d1c251",
    "reference": "1- Joshua 24:15 \u201cAs for me and my house, we will serve the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "If ye ___ the Lord, and serve strange gods, then he will turn and do you hurt, and consume you, after that he hath done you good.",
    "options": [
      "Forsake",
      "Leave",
      "Ignore",
      "Blaspheme"
    ],
    "answer": "Forsake",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ab99ad2d-456b-4306-8c20-d796167fbba7",
    "reference": "2- 2 Peter 3:9 \u201cThe Lord is not slack concerning His promise\u201d",
    "question": "Take good heed therefore unto yourselves, that ye __ the Lord your God.",
    "options": [
      "Worship",
      "Thank",
      "Sing to",
      "Love"
    ],
    "answer": "Love",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e1457d4f-a0ac-432e-ba37-3a4edc5b94db",
    "reference": "2- 2 Peter 3:9 \u201cThe Lord is not slack concerning His promise\u201d",
    "question": "But, beloved, be not ignorant of this one thing, that one day is with the Lord as a __ years",
    "options": [
      "Hundred",
      "Thousand",
      "Ten",
      "Five"
    ],
    "answer": "Thousand",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a0d7fa00-95fe-4c30-a9de-9bb623704c53",
    "reference": "2- 2 Peter 3:9 \u201cThe Lord is not slack concerning His promise\u201d",
    "question": "Nevertheless we, according to his promise, look for new ___ and a new earth, wherein dwelleth righteousness.",
    "options": [
      "Gifts",
      "Wisdom",
      "Bodies",
      "Heavens"
    ],
    "answer": "Heavens",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e205e5ba-d98c-4343-9980-53e91710db7e",
    "reference": "3- Matthew 23:11 \u201cHe who is greatest among you shall be your servant\u201d",
    "question": "But grow in __, and in the knowledge of our Lord and Savior Jesus Christ.",
    "options": [
      "Understanding",
      "Love",
      "Grace",
      "Praise"
    ],
    "answer": "Grace",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2bcd6ecc-4e93-49c0-a5df-b7ddf9140b05",
    "reference": "3- Matthew 23:11 \u201cHe who is greatest among you shall be your servant\u201d",
    "question": "Jesus said unto him, thou shalt love the Lord thy God with all thy __, and with all thy soul, and with all thy mind.",
    "options": [
      "Household",
      "Strength",
      "Being",
      "Heart"
    ],
    "answer": "Heart",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "af27ac60-bfe5-44d5-9f8c-6e0287efe190",
    "reference": "4- Deuteronomy 29:29 \u201cThe secret things belong to the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "And call no man your father upon the ___: for one is your Father, which is in heaven.",
    "options": [
      "Church",
      "Earth",
      "Community",
      "Country"
    ],
    "answer": "Earth",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3628f717-3239-4356-ae15-b7103f541c76",
    "reference": "4- Deuteronomy 29:29 \u201cThe secret things belong to the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "Keep therefore the words of this covenant, and do them, that ye may ___ in all that ye do.",
    "options": [
      "Be blessed",
      "Prosper",
      "Be honored",
      "Enjoy"
    ],
    "answer": "Prosper",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4652546f-7d5d-4d2a-b9a8-c853b3d60166",
    "reference": "4- Deuteronomy 29:29 \u201cThe secret things belong to the LORD\u201d",
    "question": "And the Lord shall ___ him unto evil out of all the tribes of Israel, according to all the curses of the covenant that are written in this book of the law.",
    "options": [
      "Delight",
      "Throw",
      "Separate",
      "Hand"
    ],
    "answer": "Separate",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1e8129bb-d109-4398-9e52-553581948930",
    "reference": "5- Luke 14:11 \u201cWhoever exalts himself will be humbled\u201d",
    "question": "Then men shall say, because they have ___ the covenant of the Lord God of their fathers, which he made with them when he brought forth out of the land of Egypt.",
    "options": [
      "Ignored",
      "Broken",
      "Cursed",
      "Forsaken"
    ],
    "answer": "Forsaken",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a51f41c5-1512-4e17-8efc-8ceccc113c68",
    "reference": "5- Luke 14:11 \u201cWhoever exalts himself will be humbled\u201d",
    "question": "And thou shalt be ___; for they cannot recompense thee: for thou shalt be recompensed at the resurrection of the just.",
    "options": [
      "Blessed",
      "Rewarded",
      "Humiliated",
      "Destroyed"
    ],
    "answer": "Blessed",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "00bb5d87-d0f0-4206-a21c-bb90d2a2c50b",
    "reference": "5- Luke 14:11 \u201cWhoever exalts himself will be humbled\u201d",
    "question": "And whosoever doth not bear his cross, and come after me, cannot be my ___.",
    "options": [
      "Servant",
      "Friend",
      "Disciple",
      "Support"
    ],
    "answer": "Disciple",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "225a2bfa-00c4-4bfb-895a-24114271b7fd",
    "reference": "6- Isaiah 53:12 \u201cChrist bore the sins of many\u201d",
    "question": "Salt is good: but if the salt have lost his ___, wherewith shall it be seasoned?",
    "options": [
      "Smell",
      "Savor",
      "Color",
      "Power"
    ],
    "answer": "Savor",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fad744af-9ca1-4089-81b4-3654c0b1d276",
    "reference": "6- Isaiah 53:12 \u201cChrist bore the sins of many\u201d",
    "question": "Surely he hath borne our ___, and carried our sorrows: yet we did esteem him stricken, smitten of God, and afflicted.",
    "options": [
      "Names",
      "Griefs",
      "Future",
      "Blessings"
    ],
    "answer": "Griefs",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "a1b091c9-c89e-4771-b001-438f4ca6d920",
    "reference": "6- Isaiah 53:12 \u201cChrist bore the sins of many\u201d",
    "question": "For ye shall not go out with haste, nor go by ___: for the Lord will go before you; and the God of Israel will be your rearward.",
    "options": [
      "Flight",
      "Shame",
      "Wickedness",
      "Suffering"
    ],
    "answer": "Flight",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7ab7c244-b6d0-44fe-bc0e-d6a44a4a5c1d",
    "reference": "6- Isaiah 53:12 \u201cChrist bore the sins of many\u201d",
    "question": "Behold, my servant shall deal prudently, he shall be ___ and extolled, and be very high.",
    "options": [
      "Worshiped",
      "Honored",
      "Exalted",
      "Loved"
    ],
    "answer": "Exalted",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "afd6e925-15ae-4361-8d75-af7cde4188eb",
    "reference": "6- Isaiah 53:12 \u201cChrist bore the sins of many\u201d",
    "question": "I have glorified thee on the earth: I have ____ the work which thou gavest me to do.",
    "options": [
      "Asked",
      "Finished",
      "Started",
      "Enjoyed"
    ],
    "answer": "Finished",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "63fd35ed-0745-49b4-b6f4-0e48e2caebf4",
    "reference": "6- Isaiah 53:12 \u201cChrist bore the sins of many\u201d",
    "question": "Who is Jesus praying for?",
    "options": [
      "The 12 disciples",
      "The world",
      "All believers",
      "For himself"
    ],
    "answer": "All believers",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "aad32c8b-dc3b-4a3b-81a1-72d273bef034",
    "reference": "8- Hebrews 11:1 \u201cFaith is the substance of things hoped for\u201d",
    "question": "Sanctify them through thy truth: thy word is ____.",
    "options": [
      "Pure",
      "Truth",
      "Unchangeable",
      "Life"
    ],
    "answer": "Truth",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8eff0ca3-35af-44ac-86a0-6f812801e47e",
    "reference": "8- Hebrews 11:1 \u201cFaith is the substance of things hoped for\u201d",
    "question": "For yet a little while, and he that shall come will come, and will not ___.",
    "options": [
      "Die",
      "Tarry",
      "Be revoked",
      "Lack"
    ],
    "answer": "Tarry",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "2ed10c77-30d8-4585-93e6-08600a4982b7",
    "reference": "8- Hebrews 11:1 \u201cFaith is the substance of things hoped for\u201d",
    "question": "How must the just live?",
    "options": [
      "By faith",
      "By trusting the Lord",
      "By hope and prayers",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "By faith",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "975ef0fd-14d1-4d3e-abe9-250596809cc1",
    "reference": "9- Psalm 20:4 \u201cMay He grant you according to your heart\u2019s desire\u201d",
    "question": "But without faith it is ___ to please him: for he that cometh to God must believe that he is, and that he is a rewarder of them that diligently seek him.",
    "options": [
      "Unbearable",
      "Impossible",
      "Possible",
      "Worthless"
    ],
    "answer": "Impossible",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "70abdcd8-0a81-4ee2-9e53-c922d016bc88",
    "reference": "9- Psalm 20:4 \u201cMay He grant you according to your heart\u2019s desire\u201d",
    "question": "Send thee help from the ___, and strengthen thee out of Zion.",
    "options": [
      "Heavens",
      "Sanctuary",
      "Church",
      "None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "Sanctuary",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "084d0a5c-3c1d-464f-8956-3bce51e037a5",
    "reference": "9- Psalm 20:4 \u201cMay He grant you according to your heart\u2019s desire\u201d",
    "question": "Does the Lord save his anointed?",
    "options": [
      "Not sure",
      "Sometimes",
      "No",
      "Yes"
    ],
    "answer": "Yes",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "f3f739d9-6fd4-4407-b779-4fbe751aab16",
    "reference": "10- Psalm 37:3 \u201cTrust in the LORD and do good\"",
    "question": "___, Lord: let the king hear us when we call.",
    "options": [
      "Save",
      "Praise the",
      "Sing to the",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "937aa8c9-2ccc-4521-a0b1-f0c103f124a6",
    "reference": "10- Psalm 37:3 \u201cTrust in the LORD and do good\"",
    "question": "Let not the foot of ___ come against me, and let not the hand of the wicked remove me.",
    "options": [
      "Pride",
      "Vengeance",
      "Shame",
      "Scorn"
    ],
    "answer": "Pride",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b156b154-6b8c-4794-ad87-b08547de122c",
    "reference": "11- Matthew 26:41 \u201cWatch and pray\u201d",
    "question": "___ thy way unto the Lord; and he shall give thee the desires of thine heart.",
    "options": [
      "Hope",
      "Favor",
      "Honor",
      "Commit"
    ],
    "answer": "Commit",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "46f53440-6a96-4b80-a3e5-cc45b8066e45",
    "reference": "11- Matthew 26:41 \u201cWatch and pray\u201d",
    "question": "Who said to Jesus he would not deny him?",
    "options": [
      "John",
      "Peter",
      "Paul",
      "Judas"
    ],
    "answer": "Peter",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6ad38c2b-d303-430f-b73a-72cae2af5b31",
    "reference": "11- Matthew 26:41 \u201cWatch and pray\u201d",
    "question": "Where did Jesus take Peter, and the two sons of Zebedee to pray?",
    "options": [
      "Israel",
      "Gethsemane",
      "Egypt",
      "Jerusalem"
    ],
    "answer": "Gethsemane",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d20c1137-18e1-4420-bac0-dbf0197ed087",
    "reference": "12- Deuteronomy 31:8 \u201c[The LORD] will not leave you nor forsake you\u201d",
    "question": "But how then shall the ___ be fulfilled, that thus it must be?",
    "options": [
      "Law",
      "Scriptures",
      "Word",
      "Purpose"
    ],
    "answer": "Scriptures",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "04cc86a5-efea-4f23-8e6f-ff8e78fa9412",
    "reference": "12- Deuteronomy 31:8 \u201c[The LORD] will not leave you nor forsake you\u201d",
    "question": "Be strong and be of a good ___, fear not, nor be afraid of them: for the Lord thy God, he it is that doth go with thee; he will not fail thee, nor forsake thee.",
    "options": [
      "Understanding",
      "Standing",
      "Courage",
      "Health"
    ],
    "answer": "Courage",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "760e631d-181a-464f-8754-0dea7acc373e",
    "reference": "12- Deuteronomy 31:8 \u201c[The LORD] will not leave you nor forsake you\u201d",
    "question": "What is the year of release also known as?",
    "options": [
      "Year of the Lord",
      "Year of worship",
      "Year of cancelling debt",
      "Year of praise"
    ],
    "answer": "Year of cancelling debt",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4647a53a-0689-4ac6-b8ea-96ea84d481c9",
    "reference": "13- Exodus 13:21-22 \u201cThe LORD went before them\u201d",
    "question": "Who frequent was the year of release?",
    "options": [
      "Every year",
      "It occurred after every 10 years",
      "It occurred after every 4 years",
      "It occurred after every 7 years"
    ],
    "answer": "It occurred after every 7 years",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "b9c654c1-1bd6-4eeb-8c0c-2dfefea2806e",
    "reference": "13- Exodus 13:21-22 \u201cThe LORD went before them\u201d",
    "question": "Sanctify unto me all the ___, whatsoever openeth the womb among the children of Israel, both of man and of beast: it is mine.",
    "options": [
      "Last born",
      "First born",
      "Second born",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "First born",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4ad4218a-21ac-40e5-9564-25f609ba336f",
    "reference": "13- Exodus 13:21-22 \u201cThe LORD went before them\u201d",
    "question": "____ days thou shalt eat unleavened bread, and in the seventh day shall be a feast to the Lord.",
    "options": [
      "Seven",
      "Five",
      "Six",
      "Three"
    ],
    "answer": "Seven",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cd0a8055-f60d-4d53-997d-1ea63897bc02",
    "reference": "13- Exodus 13:21-22 \u201cThe LORD went before them\u201d",
    "question": "Now the sojourning of the children of Israel, who dwelt in Egypt, was ___ and thirty years.",
    "options": [
      "One hundred",
      "Four hundred",
      "Three hundred",
      "Two hundred"
    ],
    "answer": "Four hundred",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "851fd400-f399-44fa-989d-ee6b441598ab",
    "reference": "13- Exodus 13:21-22 \u201cThe LORD went before them\u201d",
    "question": "And the evening and the morning were the __ day.",
    "options": [
      "Fifth",
      "Second",
      "Third",
      "Fourth"
    ],
    "answer": "Fifth",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c217feaf-fb44-43c9-b399-adc9dd7feb69",
    "reference": "13- Exodus 13:21-22 \u201cThe LORD went before them\u201d",
    "question": "According to Genesis 1, did God create only male?",
    "options": [
      "No",
      "Yes",
      "It doesn\u2019t say",
      "Maybe"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c47ec780-9828-4b1b-b4cc-ffbe9a9da4dc",
    "reference": "15- Genesis 2:7 \u201cMan became a living being\u201d",
    "question": "And God blessed them, and God said unto them, be ___, and multiply, and replenish the earth, and subdue it",
    "options": [
      "Gentle",
      "Kind",
      "Fruitful",
      "Determine"
    ],
    "answer": "Fruitful",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9a43fc66-ad18-4d1f-89d9-20def1311ddd",
    "reference": "15- Genesis 2:7 \u201cMan became a living being\u201d",
    "question": "When did God rest?",
    "options": [
      "Never",
      "On the sixth day",
      "On the seventh day",
      "On the third day"
    ],
    "answer": "On the seventh day",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "d0ee625d-4f4e-4249-a163-750018dc896e",
    "reference": "16- Genesis 2:23 Woman was Formed from Man",
    "question": "Where did God put the man he created?",
    "options": [
      "On earth",
      "On a little island",
      "In Eden",
      "In the mountain"
    ],
    "answer": "In Eden",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "8ad211c4-6c16-4efa-bd98-fad6a4f3a2cf",
    "reference": "16- Genesis 2:23 Woman was Formed from Man",
    "question": "What was Adam doing when Eve was created?",
    "options": [
      "Worshipping",
      "Sleeping",
      "Singing",
      "Walking about"
    ],
    "answer": "Sleeping",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "61dd299e-3138-49f2-8674-09717ed4bbee",
    "reference": "16- Genesis 2:23 Woman was Formed from Man",
    "question": "What did Adam say when he first saw Eve?",
    "options": [
      "She\u2019s my wife",
      "She\u2019s beautiful",
      "She\u2019s bone of my bones",
      "She\u2019s different"
    ],
    "answer": "She\u2019s bone of my bones",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "efe6fce8-3314-4494-8c50-f982633ccd02",
    "reference": "16- Genesis 2:23 Woman was Formed from Man",
    "question": "According to Genesis 2 who shall leave their mother and father?",
    "options": [
      "Man",
      "Woman",
      "Man & Woman",
      "Adam"
    ],
    "answer": "Man",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "64dd5f74-6eef-4588-8f01-900006efd491",
    "reference": "16- Genesis 2:23 Woman was Formed from Man",
    "question": "What did the serpent say would happen if the woman ate the fruit?",
    "options": [
      "She\u2019ll be wise",
      "She\u2019ll surely not die",
      "She\u2019ll surely die",
      "She\u2019ll be more beautiful"
    ],
    "answer": "She\u2019ll surely not die",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "eb82d2f4-15c7-4fbd-babe-71486f49d849",
    "reference": "16- Genesis 2:23 Woman was Formed from Man",
    "question": "How is the serpent described in Genesis 3?",
    "options": [
      "Powerful",
      "Powerless",
      "More subtil than any beast",
      "Harmless"
    ],
    "answer": "More subtil than any beast",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e3117b03-55ec-48a0-b975-c9e73d5cd6c3",
    "reference": "18- Genesis 6:18 \u201cI will establish My Covenant with you\u201d",
    "question": "What happened when Adam and Eve ate the fruit?",
    "options": [
      "Their eyes were opened",
      "They realized they were naked",
      "They started praying",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "c64a92c6-eba9-4586-9a01-800ae6509ba3",
    "reference": "18- Genesis 6:18 \u201cI will establish My Covenant with you\u201d",
    "question": "Who was commanded to make an ark?",
    "options": [
      "Noah",
      "Adam",
      "Eve",
      "Abraham"
    ],
    "answer": "Noah",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9ac5286b-eef4-4b5f-b162-858bbdb180fd",
    "reference": "18- Genesis 6:18 \u201cI will establish My Covenant with you\u201d",
    "question": "Why did God ask the ark to be built?",
    "options": [
      "He wanted to send his creations to exile",
      "He wanted to show his power",
      "He wanted to send a flood to destroy those who were unfaithful",
      "For no reason"
    ],
    "answer": "He wanted to send a flood to destroy those who were unfaithful",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "01226d67-9d1b-4183-9a8b-1b3b6de298d6",
    "reference": "19- Genesis 9:1 \u201cBe fruitful and multiply\u201d",
    "question": "The earth also was ____ before God, and the earth was filled with violence.",
    "options": [
      "Dark",
      "Corrupt",
      "Empty",
      "Calm"
    ],
    "answer": "Corrupt",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "94edaa4b-66b1-41e9-a48e-e7b3f70139c5",
    "reference": "19- Genesis 9:1 \u201cBe fruitful and multiply\u201d",
    "question": "Who did God bless and commanded to be fruitful?",
    "options": [
      "Noah",
      "Noah\u2019s sons",
      "Adam",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9db16040-8b8d-4490-90d4-0ed22c04e293",
    "reference": "19- Genesis 9:1 \u201cBe fruitful and multiply\u201d",
    "question": "Who is the father of Canaan?",
    "options": [
      "Noah",
      "Shem",
      "Ham",
      "Japheth"
    ],
    "answer": "Ham",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ea3893b8-e48d-444c-b59b-4db9b76295e9",
    "reference": "20- Genesis 12:1-2 \u201cI will bless you and make your name great\u201d",
    "question": "While the earth remaineth, ____ and harvest, and cold and heat, and summer and winter, and day and night shall not cease.",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Seedtime",
      "Judgement",
      "Blessing"
    ],
    "answer": "Seedtime",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "cdc30990-d9e6-4ee2-8e55-d1dd42980207",
    "reference": "20- Genesis 12:1-2 \u201cI will bless you and make your name great\u201d",
    "question": "Did God tell Abram where he was taking him?",
    "options": [
      "No",
      "Yes",
      "It is not clear",
      "Yes, in Jerusalem"
    ],
    "answer": "No",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7abed4c0-b228-4ba0-85d8-7182b70a1407",
    "reference": "20- Genesis 12:1-2 \u201cI will bless you and make your name great\u201d",
    "question": "Which of these blessings did God not pronounced on Abram?",
    "options": [
      "You will be a great nation",
      "I will make you king",
      "Your name will be great",
      "You will a blessing"
    ],
    "answer": "I will make you king",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "dff1584d-8fcc-46aa-869e-1a34b619afb3",
    "reference": "20- Genesis 12:1-2 \u201cI will bless you and make your name great\u201d",
    "question": "What was the name of Sarai\u2019s handmaid?",
    "options": [
      "Hagar",
      "Esther",
      "Eva",
      "Judith"
    ],
    "answer": "Hagar",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fb28742b-e8fe-4787-b89e-ceb5d2008b46",
    "reference": "20- Genesis 12:1-2 \u201cI will bless you and make your name great\u201d",
    "question": "What was the name of Abram first child?",
    "options": [
      "Isaack",
      "Ishmael",
      "Jacob",
      "Moses"
    ],
    "answer": "Ishmael",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0f51fd31-3bfe-49ad-b455-a7d4e47babcb",
    "reference": "22- Genesis 17:10 \u201cThis is My Covenant Which You Shall Keep\u201d",
    "question": "And Abram was fourscore and ___ years old, when Hagar bare Ishmael to Abram",
    "options": [
      "75",
      "21",
      "6",
      "88"
    ],
    "answer": "6",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "943060c3-b0e0-4097-ab1b-e493f63ea577",
    "reference": "22- Genesis 17:10 \u201cThis is My Covenant Which You Shall Keep\u201d",
    "question": "And I will make my covenant between me and thee, and will ___ thee excedingly",
    "options": [
      "Honor",
      "Bless",
      "Punish",
      "Multiply"
    ],
    "answer": "Multiply",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1e273b9b-19fd-4734-9ae0-3f293cdc9743",
    "reference": "22- Genesis 17:10 \u201cThis is My Covenant Which You Shall Keep\u201d",
    "question": "What was Abram name changed to?",
    "options": [
      "Israel",
      "Abraham",
      "Eli",
      "Victor"
    ],
    "answer": "Abraham",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "9a80bf31-6502-4c50-8f2b-981fc4a28c43",
    "reference": "23- Genesis 18:14 \u201cIs anything too hard for the LORD?\u201d",
    "question": "What was to be the sign of covenant between God and Abram?",
    "options": [
      "Love",
      "Worship",
      "Circumcision",
      "Nothing"
    ],
    "answer": "Circumcision",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "1849f8f8-5435-4db0-b787-f477d6ba2726",
    "reference": "23- Genesis 18:14 \u201cIs anything too hard for the LORD?\u201d",
    "question": "What was Sarah reaction when the servant of God said she would have a child?",
    "options": [
      "She laughed",
      "She was excited",
      "She was moody",
      "She bless the servant"
    ],
    "answer": "She laughed",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ec07091c-a369-4090-b878-726ab1e997fa",
    "reference": "24- 1 Kings 4:29 \u201cGod gave Solomon wisdom and exceedingly great understanding\u201d",
    "question": "And the Lord said, shall I __ from Abraham that thing which I do.",
    "options": [
      "Proclaim",
      "Reveal",
      "Hide",
      "Share"
    ],
    "answer": "Hide",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "fc25d9b2-777f-464b-9747-6ffb018a4f22",
    "reference": "24- 1 Kings 4:29 \u201cGod gave Solomon wisdom and exceedingly great understanding\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Jehoshaphat\u2019s father?",
    "options": [
      "Solomon",
      "Zadok",
      "Paruah",
      "Shishad"
    ],
    "answer": "Paruah",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "4368b810-2b5b-4291-90f5-a3836cd646cc",
    "reference": "24- 1 Kings 4:29 \u201cGod gave Solomon wisdom and exceedingly great understanding\u201d",
    "question": "How many proverbs did Solomon speak?",
    "options": [
      "Hundred",
      "Three thousand",
      "Three hundred",
      "One thousand"
    ],
    "answer": "Three thousand",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "05f3c3eb-8986-452c-ad9a-2beb7dc49d2f",
    "reference": "25- Proverbs 1:1-4 The Proverbs of Solomon",
    "question": "How many songs did Solomon have?",
    "options": [
      "Hundred",
      "Thousand",
      "Five",
      "Thousand and five"
    ],
    "answer": "Thousand and five",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "85024ab9-1fdf-4eaa-b2cd-b17616a2bbc6",
    "reference": "25- Proverbs 1:1-4 The Proverbs of Solomon",
    "question": "Who was Solomon\u2019s father?",
    "options": [
      "King David",
      "Abraham",
      "Judas",
      "Moses"
    ],
    "answer": "King David",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "223fba79-2df2-497c-b9af-09a8c8957ad8",
    "reference": "25- Proverbs 1:1-4 The Proverbs of Solomon",
    "question": "A wise man will hear, and will increase ___; and a man of understanding shall attain unto wise counsels.",
    "options": [
      "Knowledge",
      "Learning",
      "Wisdom",
      "Appreciation"
    ],
    "answer": "Learning",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "bd5b4ae1-3bfd-4737-a45f-f24f1c4ce377",
    "reference": "26- Matthew 12:42 Seek the Wisdom of Solomon",
    "question": "My son, hear the instruction of thy ___, and forsake not the law of thy mother.",
    "options": [
      "Family",
      "Pastor",
      "Father",
      "Friend"
    ],
    "answer": "Father",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "86233d7a-ee9c-4dd7-b7d8-f584352fb6e4",
    "reference": "26- Matthew 12:42 Seek the Wisdom of Solomon",
    "question": "How is a tree known?",
    "options": [
      "By its kind",
      "By its name",
      "By its fruit",
      "By its location"
    ],
    "answer": "By its fruit",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "711d8d6b-00bf-4da5-9d51-c1ca9e408ac7",
    "reference": "26- Matthew 12:42 Seek the Wisdom of Solomon",
    "question": "For out of the abundance of the heart the mouth ____.",
    "options": [
      "Sing",
      "Speaketh",
      "Whispered",
      "Eat"
    ],
    "answer": "Speaketh",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3e402193-d4f7-41d2-ac1b-fd4a66da798a",
    "reference": "27- 1 Kings 3:6-15 \u201cI have given you a wise and understanding heart\u201d",
    "question": "Who does Jesus say is his brother, sister, and mother?",
    "options": [
      "Those that are born in Israel",
      "Those who know him",
      "Those that do the will of his Father (God)",
      "Those that go to church"
    ],
    "answer": "Those that do the will of his Father (God)",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "7c701a6e-dbd0-4dd9-baaf-b1276157f90f",
    "reference": "27- 1 Kings 3:6-15 \u201cI have given you a wise and understanding heart\u201d",
    "question": "Where did the Lord appear to Solomon in a dream?",
    "options": [
      "Gibeon",
      "Canaan",
      "Jerusalem",
      "Eden"
    ],
    "answer": "Gibeon",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "0574e1a5-dd0e-4091-bfa9-1416227ed277",
    "reference": "27- 1 Kings 3:6-15 \u201cI have given you a wise and understanding heart\u201d",
    "question": "What did Solomon ask of the Lord?",
    "options": [
      "Money",
      "Understanding",
      "Fame",
      "Power"
    ],
    "answer": "Understanding",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "af5ad083-83f6-4de9-ac08-bfbc3b251675",
    "reference": "28-Proverbs 2:6 \u201cThe LORD gives wisdom\u201d",
    "question": "Who was Benaiah\u2019s father?",
    "options": [
      "Jehoiada",
      "Solomon",
      "Zadok",
      "Shishad"
    ],
    "answer": "Jehoiada",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "aa8f98e1-3efa-467d-af9e-ccb82777f752",
    "reference": "28-Proverbs 2:6 \u201cThe LORD gives wisdom\u201d",
    "question": "Who gives wisdom?",
    "options": [
      "Learning",
      "Our prayers",
      "God",
      "Faithfulness"
    ],
    "answer": "God",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "6c697691-92d4-4234-9d52-7a166f08770e",
    "reference": "29- 2 Chronicles 1:8-12 \u201cLet your promise \u2026 be established; give me wisdom and knowledge\u201d",
    "question": "So that thou incline, thine ear unto wisdom, and apply thine heart to ___.",
    "options": [
      "Knowledge",
      "Wisdom",
      "Understanding",
      "Creativity"
    ],
    "answer": "Understanding",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "de97c6e5-1546-4c93-b0f1-0c7917b9576c",
    "reference": "29- 2 Chronicles 1:8-12 \u201cLet your promise \u2026 be established; give me wisdom and knowledge\u201d",
    "question": "What did Solomon ask of God?",
    "options": [
      "Knowledge",
      "Wisdom",
      "Fame",
      "a & b"
    ],
    "answer": "a & b",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "ddf16074-24f1-460b-9c4c-ea6670d0c688",
    "reference": "30- 2 Kings 17:35 \u201cYou shall not fear other gods\u201d",
    "question": "Apart from granting Solomon request, what else did God promise him?",
    "options": [
      "Riches",
      "Wealth",
      "Honor",
      "All the above"
    ],
    "answer": "All the above",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e2024fab-a5f7-4371-a283-f51ffedfcdd8",
    "reference": "30- 2 Kings 17:35 \u201cYou shall not fear other gods\u201d",
    "question": "For how long did the king of Assyria besiege Samaria?",
    "options": [
      "5 years",
      "3 years",
      "21 years",
      "7 days"
    ],
    "answer": "3 years",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "e166ab22-ff9a-4e5b-b5d3-6dba21113fda",
    "reference": "30- 2 Kings 17:35 \u201cYou shall not fear other gods\u201d",
    "question": "Why was the Lord angry against Israel?",
    "options": [
      "They worshipped idols",
      "They didn\u2019t care for God",
      "They were rebellious",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "They worshipped idols",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  },
  {
    "id": "3312aa7a-cf6e-4d6a-84b0-ab88989235e8",
    "reference": "30- 2 Kings 17:35 \u201cYou shall not fear other gods\u201d",
    "question": "Who were Adrammelech and Anammelech?",
    "options": [
      "The high priests",
      "Sorcerers",
      "The gods of Sepharvaim",
      "The servants of God"
    ],
    "answer": "The gods of Sepharvaim",
    "quarter": "Q2",
    "month": ""
  }
]